<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[What happens here, stays in here.]]></title>
  <link href="http://sunus.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sunus.me/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-17T03:26:10+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://sunus.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[sunus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a LAN with multiple gateway/interface with iptables and route policy under awesome Linux]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2013/03/17/setting-up-a-lan-with-multiple-gateway-slash-interface-with-iptables-and-route-policy/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-17T22:09:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2013/03/17/setting-up-a-lan-with-multiple-gateway-slash-interface-with-iptables-and-route-policy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Introduction</h2>

<p>First of all, it all because my MacBookPro&#8217;s xl2tp utils can not work under my school&#8217;s networking enviroment. so this is how the post is born.</p>

<p>I have been digging with those stuffs for almost a week, and now, finally i get it rolling and it seems awesome. this post will talks about netfilter known as iptables and ip route policy. and some technic/tool like tcpdump will be involved as well.</p>

<h2>Environment</h2>

<p>The environment i have is like this below:</p>

<pre><code>-----------------    -----------------
| Slow          |    | Fast          |
| Internet-1    |    | Internet-2    |
| 10.10.149.1   |    | 123.150.232.1 |
-----------------    -----------------
         |             |
[eth0.2] |             |[ppp0]
         |             |
        --------------------------
        | Route, Running Linux   |
        | br-lan: 192.168.1.1    | [br-lan]      ------------------------
        | ppp0:   123.150.232.74 | --------------| Other Machines in Lan|
        | eth0.2: 10.10.149.4    |               |-----------------------
        --------------------------
        |                        |
[br-lan]|                        |[br-lan]
        |                        |
        |                        |
        |                        |
  -------------------------      ----------------------
  |ArchLinux              |      | MacBook            |
  |eth0: 192.168.1.245    |      | en0:192.168.1.169  |
  |ppp0: 180.134.135.173  |      |                    |
  -------------------------      ----------------------
        |
        |
        |
        |
  ------------------
  | Fast           |
  | Internet-3     |
  | 180.134.135.1  |
  ------------------
</code></pre>

<p>   after connect the wires. there is three <strong> physic wires </strong>:</p>

<ul>
<li><strong>Route</strong> <------> <strong>Slow Internet-1 </strong>this is the only one that connects to outside my dorm. via route&#8217;s port WAN.</li>
<li><strong>Route</strong> <------> <strong> ArchLinux </strong> this one is in a Route&#8217;s port #1 LAN</li>
<li><strong>Route</strong> <------> <strong> MacBook </strong> same as above, using Route&#8217;s port #2 LAN</li>
</ul>


<p>  There is also something to be noticed:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>the <strong>ppp0</strong> in <strong>Route</strong> is a high-speed connection(VPN). it needs to go though <strong>eth0.2</strong> to connect the VPN-server, then it will generate a Virtual Network InterFace, that is, ppp0.</p></li>
<li><p>the another <strong>ppp0</strong> in <strong>ArchLinux</strong> is also the high-speed connection. but firstly, it goes to <strong>Route</strong>, then the VPN-server.</p></li>
<li><p>in this environment, you can consider those ppp0 as real NICs that are connected to the internet as well.</p></li>
<li><p>So, we can say eth0.2 and two ppp0 are all outgoing Interfaces.</p></li>
</ul>


<h2>Solutions</h2>

<ul>
<li><p>   I repeat what i want to accomplished here:</p>

<p>   1 .    i want my MacBook can connected to the internet.</p>

<p>   2 .    i want my MacBook&#8217;s internet connection to be as <strong>FAST</strong> as possible.</p></li>
<li><p>   Before we get started, there&#8217;s something we can do and can&#8217;t do, in general.</p>

<p>   1 .    Seting the <strong>default route</strong> to 180.134.135.1 for ArchLinux and a route to lan. We do this because we want all the trafftic goes to a fast internet connecting while we keep the connection to the other machines in the lan still work.</p>

<pre><code># route add -net 192.168.1.0/24 gw 192.168.1.1 dev eth0
# route add default gw 180.134.135.1 dev ppp0
</code></pre>

<p>   2 .    Because there is other machines in the lan, so we can not set 123.150.232.1 as <strong>default route</strong> for Route, just like the ArchLinux. there is only <strong> me </strong> can access the Fast Internet-2.( The <strong>Benefit</strong> of being me or with me :) lol! )</p></li>
</ul>


<h3>The Slow Solution</h3>

<ul>
<li><p>   Making the MacBook can connect to the internet, but it just too slow for me. Just set up machines and route like the diagram above, it will result this:</p>

<p>   1 .  the ArchLinux using Internet-3.</p>

<p>   2 .  the MacBookPro using Slow-Internet-1</p></li>
</ul>


<h3>The A Little Bit Faster Solution</h3>

<ul>
<li><p>   Making the MacBook Using ArchLinux&#8217;s Internet-3 and the ArchLinux still keep unchanged in Slow Solution. This solution requires those steps.</p>

<ul>
<li><p>  in the MacBook, change default route from 192.168.1.1 to 192.168.1.245</p>

<p> In MacBook:
 # route add default 192.168.1.245
 # route del default 192.168.1.1</p></li>
<li><p>  in ArchLinux, set up a route policy/rule</p>

<ul>
<li><p>  the packets that comes from MacBook(192.168.1.169), Using the gateway of Internet-3.</p>

<pre><code>In ArchLinux:
# add a empty table to route table
echo '7375 SunusRules' &gt;&gt; /etc/iproute2/rt_tables
# add a default route rule to newly create table SunusRules
ip route add default via 180.134.135.173 dev ppp0 table SunusRules
# add this table to routing rules, all the packet comes from MacBook, apply this route rule.
ip rule add from 192.168.1.169 table SunusRules
</code></pre></li>
<li><p> We are done here.</p></li>
<li><p> In fact, i don&#8217;t think add a route rule here is necessarily, but anyway, it&#8217;s a good time to get the first impression of what this can do. which we will make the best use of it in next Solution.</p></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h3>The Ultimate And More Fast Solution</h3>

<ul>
<li><p>   As you may think, why we still didn&#8217;t use Fast-Internet-2 yet. Now, it&#8217;s time to rolling on this connection! Let the MacBook and only MacBook use this connection.</p>

<ul>
<li><p> In fact, this is a kinda complicated process, we need to do the following stuffs to put it all together to work properly.</p>

<p> 1 . Leave MacBook&#8217;s default (192.168.1.1) untouched.</p>

<p> 2 . Let the Route know, if a packet is come from MacBook(192.168.1.169), sets the <strong>Gateway</strong> of this connection to 1123.150.232.1 and <strong>Outgoing Interface</strong> to ppp0. because at this point, only ppp0 can connect to it&#8217;s <strong>Gateway</strong>(123.150.232.1)</p>

<ul>
<li>  <strong>policy routing</strong> is the first magic.

<ul>
<li>as most of us might already knew that, the linux kernel only allow exactly one <strong>efficient default</strong> in <strong>route table</strong>.</li>
<li>so this needs is beyond a simple <code>route</code> command can do. but, don&#8217;t worry. net-tools is out of date for so long, let us introduce the new <code>ip</code> tools to do this for us.</li>
<li>basically, this is still maintain that one kernel default route in route table, but, it allow us to add custom route table based on our needs, and set up the right condition. e.g <strong>the packet&#8217;s source address/net</strong> or <strong>the incoming interface</strong>, etc see <code>ip route help</code>.

<ul>
<li><p>the steps to make this happened are:</p>

<pre><code># add a table id and table name to the route table database, just make sure they are unique.
echo '7375 sunusroute' &gt;&gt; /etc/iproute2/rt_tables
# check if that succeeded, the out should be empty.
ip route show table sunusroute
# then, add route rules to this newly create table.
# set the default route/gateway of this table
ip route add default via 123.150.232.1 dev ppp0
# finally, add a rule to tell the kernel, under what circumstance,
the packet should use the route table from what we just set,
instead of the default route rules. we just set this simple rule, if a packet is from 192.168.1.169, then apply the rules in route table sunusroute.
ip rule add from 192.168.1.169 table sunusroute
</code></pre></li>
<li><p>check if those are valid by:</p>

<pre><code>ip rule show
&gt;&gt; 0: from all lookup local
&gt;&gt; 32761: from 192.168.1.169 lookup sunusroute
&gt;&gt; many-more-lines-of-other-rules
ip route show table sunusroute
&gt;&gt; default via 123.150.108.1 dev ppp0
ip route flush cache
</code></pre></li>
<li><p>the last command <code>ip route flush cache</code> is just a precaution, in case the old rules in cache might do something nasty.</p></li>
<li><p>we are done in this step.</p></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<p> 3 . Also, Since the Route&#8217;s default gateway isn&#8217;t 123.150.232.1, so it&#8217;s a must to set packet&#8217;s <strong>source address</strong> to 123.150.232.74. so here we will do a <strong>SNAT</strong> magic.</p>

<ul>
<li><p>we are officially meet the iptables here, the firewall of the linux, a great tool for many other usages as well.</p>

<ul>
<li>the iptables consists by some tables, and those tables has some chains. the packet need to go all the way from the very first chain to the very last one. so that this packet can be send/receive correctly. during the packet&#8217;s travel in those tables and chains, it might be modify, accept, drop or reject, we can even add marks to those packets so that we can debug them.</li>
<li>here is a brief image of how a packets goes.</li>
</ul>


<p><img src="http://sunus.me/images/iptables_traverse.jpg" title="iptables_traverse" alt="alt text" /></p>

<ul>
<li>obviously, what we want the route to do is:</li>
</ul>


<p><strong>forward the packets from 192.168.1.169 to interface ppp0 with the right gateway 123.150.231.1</strong></p>

<ul>
<li><p>follow the diagram, the packets should go through the tables and chains in the order of</p>

<ol>
<li>[packet come in from ppp0]</li>
<li>[raw-PREROUTING]</li>
<li>[mangle-PREROUTING]</li>
<li>[filter-PREROUTING]</li>
<li>[ROUTING-DESICION]</li>
<li>[mangle-FORWARD]</li>
<li>[filter-FORWARD]</li>
<li>[ROUTING-DESICION]</li>
<li>[mangle-POSTROUTING]</li>
<li>[nat-POSTROUTING]</li>
<li>[packet come out from ppp0]</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li><p>I once not sure/doubt about what those <strong>ROUTING-DESICION</strong> do, after my research, i think it&#8217;s just decide what <strong>route</strong> to use, basically, it just look up the routing table and get a <strong>route</strong> to use.</p></li>
<li><p>so, what we need to do is, change the packets&#8217;s source address right after the packet go off. that is, in the step ten.</p>

<p> <code>iptables -t nat -o ppp0 -j SNAT --to-address 123.150.232.74</code></p></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<p> 4 . We&#8217;re pretty much done here:)</p>

<p> 5 . Enjoy!</p></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h2>More useful resources.</h2>

<h3>i read a lot of them to make this work, i think you should do that, too. if you want to fully utilize your network.</h3>

<ol>
<li><p>the <strong>iptable-tutorial</strong></p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.frozentux.net/documents/iptables-tutorial">http://www.frozentux.net/documents/iptables-tutorial/</a>

<ul>
<li>pretty much every chapter is worthing reading :)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><p>the awesome and notable <strong>Linux Advanced Routing &amp; Traffic Control</strong>, aka &#8216;lartc&#8217;</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://lartc.org">http://lartc.org</a>

<ul>
<li>especially chapter 4 and 11 are much involved in this post.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><p><strong>much more</strong> you will find in those two above.</p></li>
<li><p>1,2 also have Chinese version, thank for those guy who do the translation work!</p></li>
</ol>


<h2>PS</h2>

<h3>since i now got kinda <em>experience</em> of doing those stuffs, you are welcome to leave a message or just email me about what you think or what you want to do. i will try to help you if i can.</h3>

<h3>ANY questions and discussion are welcomed, too.</h3>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[That could be Interesting! I guess.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2013/02/24/that-could-be-interesting-i-guess/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-24T23:58:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2013/02/24/that-could-be-interesting-i-guess</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong> Long time no see </strong></p>

<ul>
<li><p>Hi, there! First of all, happy new year to you and wish you all have a wonderful new year, i give you my very best wishes here:)
Yeah, i did quit my job last year and had theses about 40 days of <strong>AWESOME</strong> holidays in my hometown with my family and friends which is fun and happy. We went to couple of places with views, of course, i took some photos, too. But most of those photos are mountains and some kind of <strong>vulgar</strong> pictures. LOL</p></li>
<li><p>Besides of having fun, i got my MacBook, it&#8217;s a whole new user experiences, which i can not tell it&#8217;s better that Linux or not. but compare to Windows. it&#8217;s definitely a piece of work. Windows sucks, i said it to all the people i care about! :) I am getting used to OS X and i think it&#8217;s more comfortable to develop some <strong>app</strong> on that machine than my old laptop. But it&#8217;s okay, i do Linux-related/python work on my old machine while i am also a newcomer of APP developing. i am getting my motivations back, it just feel much better that i want to and CAN code again!</p></li>
<li><p>Tomorrow i will fly back to school and i don&#8217;t know what that is, i am leading some students to launch a <strong>OpenStack</strong> project in school, even though i don&#8217;t think that will be too much difficult for me, given the current situation we have. but still, i will do the most major work. don&#8217;t know it&#8217;s good for me or not, just wait and see how it goes. Also, i want some nice <strong>girls</strong> who&#8217;s interested in front-end to help me, i don&#8217;t know if she exists in my school.</p></li>
<li><p>Finally, the same-old-boring topic, i can not stop thinking about her, i know she also had a great great time on holiday, she sure did! so, let&#8217;s just hope she is still available. I even pray for that in a old temple. kidding! i didn&#8217;t do that:) so, still, chances are slim but i still don&#8217;t want to give up on this girl who had stolen my heart for months, in some point stolen my codes as well:&lt; hoping i can make this right. We didn&#8217;t send a word to each other in this whole holiday and i am not sure if she still remember me or not. but, i had hard time picking gifts for her and lucky(or not?) enough, i got something gift picking advice from my friends and sisters. so, just wait and see if she like that or not.</p></li>
<li><p>I am Back and I miss you all! the new semester could be a interesting one, not because of the school or class but you and all the uncertain changes and opportunity i wanted for a while!!</p></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pull Yourself Together]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/12/30/pull-yourself-together/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-30T00:11:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/12/30/pull-yourself-together</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4>Making Changes</h4>

<p>Yes, i am writing this blog using <strong>EMACS</strong>, the ultimate text editor, i am so umfamiliar with it right now, but, i am getting better:)</p>

<p>A lot stuffs going on lately, i&#8217;ve been weighed the pros and cons about some certain things for quite a long time.
But now, I don&#8217;t think i will <strong>LOST</strong> again, because i believe i made the right decision, just like the one i made in 2010.
With no regrets but only excitement. I know this will become all new to me, since i regain my love for this university, which i&#8217;ve called it CRAPLAND for so long. I am really looking forward to what is happening next, i bet you will, too.</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Career</p>

<p>  The first and foremost one is about my intern, or i&#8217;d prefer to called it <strong>career</strong> :)</p>

<p>  I decided to <strong>quit</strong>, if school not kick me out right now.</p>

<p>  I love my development team, my leader and brothers. yeah, we&#8217;ve became really really close friends!</p>

<p>  I love what i do and what i will do if i remain stay there, that&#8217;s something i wish i could get hands on in a year ago, and i finally get the chance to play with it. the Amazing linux kernel, filesystem, and Networking stuffs.
And i will definitely take that offer if i got it six month ago, i wanted to write some serious code back then, besides the payment is good.</p>

<p>  but, everything has a beginning has an end, that&#8217;s how things work and i can only accept it. Since, i am no longer the guy i was six month ago, i am <strong>less</strong> motivated, but i will change.</p>

<p>  That change will not happen if i stay in company, or Beijing. and a <strong>push</strong> just came in time, letting me easier to make the call.</p>

<p>  So, here i am, back to Tianjin and hopefully i can pull myself together soon.</p>

<p>  And, I am gonna thank those guy who along the way with me, helping me making the decisions, thank you!</p></li>
<li><p>Myself</p>

<p>  I wanted this subtitle as &#8216;Relationship&#8217; or something like that, but it&#8217;s okay, it&#8217;s kinda a problem of mine and I have to deal with it very carefully and hopefully it turn out to be good.</p>

<p>  I really really miss her during the days i was in Beijing, just right after i finished the project in company, i keep thinking about her. i can help myself.</p>

<p>  luckily i got some chances to see her sometimes, those moments are wonderful and I want more.</p>

<p>  We use to hang out frequently and maybe that why i am always motivated back in the days i am in school, it&#8217;s a huge lose if i can not have that anymore:(</p>

<p>  We had pizza at <strong>pizzahut</strong> last night, and walked in the snow, talking and laughing about her exs and some of my awkward stories. for quite a long i always thought we&#8217;ve never went out on rain or something like that, but this time we got snow, white, pretty snow. so, overall it&#8217;s feels nice! I never walk with a girl in the snow, so, luckily me, for i picked the right day. but, i was planed to buy her something, just like the story we talked earlier, it&#8217;s about a couple in a shop, the boy buy girl a cloth while she is trying it in changing room, and after she came out, the boy ask the girl to run, like escape and steal that cloth. yeah, i actually planned to do that, but.. we didn&#8217;t find a nice shop yesterday night:(</p>

<ul>
<li>NOTES

<ol>
<li><p>Our first official date was go to the movie, after we brought the tickets, i suggested we eat at pizzahut nearby the theater, but then she wanted to eat at a cheaper restaurant &#8220;yoshinoya&#8221;. at that time i thought maybe she don&#8217;t want me to spend too much money on our first date, but it just turned out that she is just <strong>simply</strong> don&#8217;t like pizzahut:(</p></li>
<li><p>That movie is total crap, we were all confused about that movies.</p></li>
<li><p>I still keep those tickets. the <strong>only</strong> movie we watch together.</p></li>
<li><p>I thought she loves going to the movies, in fact, she doesn&#8217;t and i, ask her to movies for like thousand times.. silly me!!</p></li>
<li><p>I asked her to movie again, TODAY.. dumb, no wonder her dump you in the first place. :(:(</p></li>
<li><p>NOTES above shows I need to get to know her more!</p></li>
</ol>
</li>
</ul>


<p>  but, the sad part is, i don&#8217;t know when we can meet again and this is really bothering me. i didn&#8217;t cherish the time we had before and took it for grant for so long. anyway, new year is about to come and i will post later.</p></li>
</ul>


<h3>God! I Love School, It Feels so good!</h3>

<h2>End of my first EMACS POST, there will be more</h2>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[hello octopress!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/12/09/hello-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-09T15:17:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/12/09/hello-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How this blog looks? i think it&#8217;s awesome!</p>

<p>it&#8217;s powered by <strong>Octopress</strong> and <strong>jekyll</strong> with <strong>git</strong> to do those maintain jobs.</p>

<p>just enjoy this brand new blog:)</p>

<p>BTW, I am having great fun at Tianjin now.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[you are the source of my source.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/12/02/you-are-the-source-of-my-source/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-02T09:52:02+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/12/02/you-are-the-source-of-my-source</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hi you, sorry i recently had so much stuffs want to write, but i again again to tell myself, you have gotta learn the iptables first, then move this blog with the domain to a new place, then write. but, i just found out it doesn&#8217;t really have much to do with the iptables, it&#8217;s apache that do the job. so, i give myself sometime to set up the apache, meanwhile, write those post while i still can remember things:)</p>

<p>first of all, i had great fun at Dec 11, knows as 11.11. i hung out with a very close friend, and we had great meal and watched the moveie The Bourne Legacy, even thought i watched this movie before, but, it&#8217;s okay to watch it again, when you have someone to keep you company:) i knew she had some difficult time with study and the other stuffs, but, anyway. Since we both knew the 11.11 means nothing to us, it just make this day much easier. i had the girl i care about and she had a boyfriend she love very much:) so, i think i am not the ones who got a reason to celebrity that day, because i am FALLING IN LOVE with someone, and i think now everyone knows that. but anway, who needs another friends when you had a friend like she, it just make my life easier, at least when i felt down, she&#8217;s always the one i can talk to. and she understand me more than any of my friends do.</p>

<p>then, back to a another topic. i can not focus on coding recently, lucky enough, i got Taylor Swift&#8217;s songs and coffee, but, i just miss her more and more, she is such  a awesome girl and i never met a girl like her before. and all of a suddenly, when i walk on the road to eat, i came up with this one:</p>

<p>&#8220;she is the source of my source, sorry about the bugs, blame her!&#8221;</p>

<p>i even post a question on Quora, to see and share with other programmers who feel the same way:</p>

<p><a href="http://www.quora.com/Programmers/Are-there-any-romantic-programming-programmer-quotes">http://www.quora.com/Programmers/Are-there-any-romantic-programming-programmer-quotes</a></p>

<p>i really really wish i can spend more that with her, when i had chance, to tell her how i felt about her, face to face.</p>

<p>and another topic, about her, again,(why always her!!) now, i just can not figure out what is REALLY going on, so, wish me luck.</p>

<p>i watch a short video &#8220;The Last&#8221;</p>

<p><a href="http://v.youku.com/v_show/id_XNDc3NTg4MjAw.html">http://v.youku.com/v_show/id_XNDc3NTg4MjAw.html</a></p>

<p>it&#8217;s about a guy&#8217;s view on his previous girlfriends and i somehow, want to write one too, even though, i am still alone now.</p>

<p>my version is about some programming language i know and how i felt about them, but trust me, in fact, it&#8217;s</p>

<p>not about programming language, it&#8217;s about her and some other girls:)</p>

<p>the last is about some options i got and i can not decided which one to choose yet. it really kills me, so, i will let</p>

<p>you know when i make the final decision:)</p>

<p>good night:)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[You made the CRAPLAND a better place]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/11/01/270/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-01T09:13:23+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/11/01/270</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi, I just got back from Tianjin and had some great meat with my friends from my dev team. I&#8217;d been in school like in five days or so, it&#8217;s strange I didn&#8217;t call it crapland :( and here is why I don&#8217;t call it crapland:
First of all, finally, after about half years long waiting, I got a chance to meet Vivian again, yeah, because I really can not come up with any new words to describe her, but, I am lucky enough to see her again. so  thrilled I got the last night before  head off, I just could not sleep and get up very early then just begin to run, Ok, that&#8217;s a little fake:( I didn&#8217;t run. Then, the funny thing is when I just get out of my apartment, I got a feeling like, someone&#8217;s  Dear PERIOD is about to come, and It turned out I was right, The one, the girl I&#8217;ve been miss for so long, got her PERIOD to visit, just one or more hours  ahead of me to see her. so, I wait one more extra day to spend with my friends. that&#8217;s the my 1st day in Tianjin.(Saturday).</p>

<p>Sunday, it&#8217;s absolutely the highlight of this short visit. When I just woke up, seeing my phone got a new  text, somehow I just feel, (AGAIN, how amazing is that?!) it&#8217;s none other than the girl I dream about, finally, gave me a chance to meet her again, just like the old days. Then I had the best three hours of this visit.she showed me some of her designs, even though I am not a fashion guy at all:) but I can tell, she love her works, just like I love my code:) and we went to the drinking shop we used to visit a lot, then, went back to school because she&#8217;s got class to take. also, just like the old days.</p>

<p>P.S.: The only program I wrote those days is the one I call &#8220;wesaid&#8221; in my phone, i wrote this on the first day of this short trip, the night before i meet  you., I use &#8220;wesaid&#8221; to remind me what we said in the last years, on the exact same day. this program intent to be UN-expandable, meaning this is for one phone number and one phone number only, and i won&#8217;t use this on other girls, i promise:) it&#8217;s too dangerous.</p>

<p>and the next a few days was kinda interesting, too. in fact, I know &#8220;MISS Hot Heart Classmate&#8221; for  about a year, we met, passed by for so many times, which leads me became more and more interested about her, and want to get to know her better, Luckily, I ask her out at a &#8220;Perfect Right time&#8221;, her  class was kinda late, she&#8217;s kinda hungry and she loves the hot pot. So, we had a night of hot pot, and we talk a lot, definitely more friendly, interesting more those new-just-get-to-know-couples.  it&#8217;s like a date but I think we both agree that&#8217;s not a date, still, it&#8217;s fun to finally get to know her,  and her didn&#8217;t disappoint me at all, she&#8217;s interested with beautiful smile, and got talent for telling/creating jokes :>
but, I doubt she is good at C programming<sup>^</sup>
and next a few days got little bored but it&#8217;s ok:)
and finally, i get back to Beijing and post this blog. good night. and hope i can see you guys again, soon:)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[i am feeling great!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/09/29/i-am-feeling-great/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-29T09:19:16+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/09/29/i-am-feeling-great</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hi, i am back to write some post again:)</p>

<p>it&#8217;s the 3rd or 4th blog since a started this kinda life at Beijing, and it&#8217;s just, humm, let&#8217;s say it&#8217;s very special times i had. i had some troubles in school, which i really don&#8217;t give it a shit about, and besides, my intern-ship is quite smoothy, or at least i think it that way. our product is about to release at the part that i covered, it looks good to me, even thought that part wasn&#8217;t as mush attractive as kernel and filesystem to me, which i am about to get really deep into those stuffs, but anyway, it&#8217;s gonna end. and i now can really put myself into the field that i love best.</p>

<p>i made some really great friends here, a very lovely girl live across my room, and she can cook for me sometimes, even thought it&#8217;s not that yummy:( and , oh, she&#8217;s a nice and beautiful girl, but, i know we will never hit it off, so, just keep that way and it&#8217;s good. at least i have a good roommate &amp; friends:)</p>

<p>and i also made friends with the guys in our development team, they are really really nice to me, even thought some of them are elder than me, but, yeah, them approved/acknowledge my skills and will let me to help them to solve some problems they had. which i feel kinda proud of myself. good job out there, sunus!</p>

<p>and we hang out a lot, drinking and play polos. it&#8217;s just a lot of fun with them and i think we&#8217;ll become brothers one day;)</p>

<p>and the final, big news, i might get a chance to meet the girl of my dream, again, after she dump me months ago. who knows :(</p>

<p>wish me luck !</p>

<p>bye and wish u a happy mid-autunm festival!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[new chapter gose go :)]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/08/19/new-chapter-gose-go/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-19T21:54:11+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/08/19/new-chapter-gose-go</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>yeah, after about two months of intern-ship in Beijing, i get back to my sweet home for a couple of days.stay with my family and friends. it&#8217;s  really really happy time spent with them, and my sisters they are doing really really good so i am proud of them :) ps, i bought my mom a new SAMSUNG GALAXY smart phone using my first salary, it did feels great!</p>

<p>and my friends, yeah, i really really want them to  change their names, but i didn&#8217;t get the perfect girl i want , didn&#8217;t bring her to my city then let my friends see how awesome and amazing she is, and how lucky i am if i had a girlfriend like she:) anyway, i still like her a lot even thought i am trying really really hard to meet some new girls and hangout with them, do things we did when we first met, but, they are, they are just NOTHING ON U. and i know now, i can not forget you for sure:( i keep the movie tickets we saw together,  the birthday gifts i wished i could give you by my side,which i know you will like it, but, you never know what that is:( and i also want to finish those drinks on the street, it&#8217;s like one or two more cups, and we can get some free drinks. sorry, i can not remember the exact numbers.</p>

<p>i don&#8217;t even know whether you will read this far or not, i don&#8217;t even know whether you will ever come to this blog or not. but if you do, even if i don&#8217;t know whether you had been there for a while or not, it&#8217;s okay.  if i were you, i saw this blog and i know much this guy likes you. i will be crying:) kidding</p>

<p>and my intern-ship goes very smoothly, the company is growing and i am doing kinda good job there. so not much to talk about.</p>

<p>anyway, new chapter of my life goes on, and you are the only missing part of my new chapter.! hoping you can be in it, some day, maybe, perhaps :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[So far so good:)]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/07/30/so-far-so-good/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-30T08:38:15+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/07/30/so-far-so-good</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi, It’s been a while since the last post, isn’t it ? so many things going on those days, I got dumped , yeah, I got dumped by a very amazing and awesome girl that I’ve always talked about.</p>

<p>and some of my friends I played a lot counter-striker with are graduated from university, so no more counter-strike for a while.(OH REALL? I don’t know:D)</p>

<p>they are a bunch of nice guys and brothers to me and I am looking forward to play with them again!</p>

<p>it’s sad, but life moves on, as it always does.</p>

<p>and I came to Beijing on July 1st, (WOW! FINALLY!) I can feel that there is a very exciting , interesting and wonderful journey just right there waiting for me to explore, to experience. and I am ready to embrace all of those wonderful things! such as new opportunities, new apartments and new roommates:) i think some of them is kinda interesting, i am looking forward to meet them:)</p>

<p>let’s talk about what I did recently, finally, I choose the best offer I can get and starting to write some serious codes :) it’s fun and it just really surprise me a lot!</p>

<p>I kind of thoughts that I am kinda good at what I do, that’s coding, but when I FINALLY got here and starting working, I just found out there’s so many people are just really really good at it, too. most of them are older than me, but they just know so so so many skills than I do, I don’t know what I will become a year or two year later, hoping I can be much better than they’re now, lol !</p>

<p>the environment of my workspace is very nice, I am very very satisfied can my very first intern job can be like this. I can get a very nice sleep, and get up anytime I want, then head off to my office. because there’s no such rule that requires you have to be the office before a specific time, this is what I really love about this company! the food here is ok, but I can deal with that. by the way, the front-desk girl is kinda cute and I ACCIDENTALLY  pissed her off several times LOL!, even thought I just got here some day ago, sorry about that:(, but I really really didn’t do those things on purpose, I just don’t know much about the rules..</p>

<p>so, right now I just need to work hard and prove my worth and make more friends and pay some EXTRA attention to the relationships that may just come in, who knows LOL!</p>

<p>anyhow, I still think of you a lot, and I saw a girl like you a lot right in the subway, even thought I knew that girl isn’t you for sure, but my heart just beat faster at that moment. i now can move on with my life, hope u can do the same:)</p>

<p>see you!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOW!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/04/18/wow/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-18T06:46:56+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/04/18/wow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>it had been a while since i turned 0x16. and the last week was just AMAZING for me, and i don&#8217;t even believe everything went so smooth(or i think?) and finally, wow!</p>

<p>first of all, it all started with a mail, then i got the second mail, third&#8230;. i was kinda had doubt in myself in the first place. but now. i do know that i am useful and people want me to work with them.</p>

<p>so, i went to Beijing on Friday, took some interviews and it all went smooth. so i got several options . now i am weighting all the pros and cons. some of the options do not interests me as the others. but anyway, this time i have to made up my mind on my own and whatever it ends, i won&#8217;t regret about it.</p>

<p>Now, i was about to get the intern . Making money by doing things i&#8217;ve been loving for so long. It&#8217;s time to figure out what i need to do with that girl  i always talked about, we haven&#8217;t been talk since like a months ago. i Did made a promise to myself, don&#8217;t contact her till i get the intern, i thought it might be kinda long, but somehow, i just kinda luck. so i put this second import thing of this semester on the table. hoping she still likes me:) because i will tell her how i felt about her and what i want from her.  i don&#8217;t know how this ends, but i am kinda looking forward to that moment. even if i got the bad answer, at least i will try. i have the courage to speak it out, loudly:)</p>

<p>good night, wish u have the good luck as i did in last three days.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[0x16]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/25/0x16/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-25T08:31:32+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/25/0x16</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>humm, i feel like i am not young anymore. but, i am still doing those &#8216;young people&#8217; stuffs that i really really feel some kinda ashamed of. so, it&#8217;s time to grow up. in fact, i know i am growing up with time goes by.
in this very moment, right before i turn to 0x16, i would like to post something, something that i wanted to say several days ago.
first of all, i am so grateful for my family for they gave me a very very nice childhood. even though sometimes i felt it just not enough, but deep down in my heart, i knew they did what they could and i will always grateful for what they&#8217;ve gave to me. i just love to have them around me!
second, i&#8217;d like to thank all of my friends, for the time we spent together, for the happiness and sadness we shared. i&#8217;m really really proud of having you guys. I will do everything i can to make you feel the same way as i do, that is, i am hoping one day, you will feel proud of having me as your friend.
one last thing, i also want to end this with something suddenly came up of my head several days ago,  to my family,  friends and the ones i love:</p>

<p>i am trying hard to to a guy that deserves you.</p>

<p>because you are just so AMAZING.</p>

<p>hope i will not let you guys down before i turn to 0x17.</p>

<p>good night:)</p>

<p>END OF 0x15.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[i'd rather take 951 than 871.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/11/id-rather-take-951-than-871/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-11T08:27:40+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/11/id-rather-take-951-than-871</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hi, i&#8217;ve got a busy week, and i still got a lot of codes to write and i am happy that i still got something to do.
the project tmenny is about to launch and my resume-generator is almost finished. in the very beginning,  i was about to write it in ruby,which i just learned those days. but quickly i found out i might do this in the language i love most, that is, C. so,i wrote so much more lines of codes than ruby/python but i love the way C codes works. simple, clear and fast. and i can figure out almost what is going on under the every line of codes.that is just feels good!</p>

<p>humm, i really miss the days when we ACTUALLY hang out together last semester. sometime i don&#8217;t feel the same way
as we&#8217;re in school while i teach you some programming stuffs or just walk with you,strange.
even though i met someone new and we had great time, still i would rather going out taking 951 with you.</p>

<p>SK failed again and some of my really good friends are going to leave this school, including the one i just met, which is pretty sad for my to accept.</p>

<p>i am not quite quitting counter-strike yet, as we haven&#8217;t been &#8216;actually&#8217; &#8216;hang out&#8217; lately, it&#8217;s fun playing counter-strike on lan. but if i got chance hanging out with you, i will definitely pick you for sure. it&#8217;s just 10 times fun than just playing game with nine guys :&lt;</p>

<p>hoping i can getting in 951 soon.
good night, gotta code tomorrow.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[first blog with codes inside]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/02/28/test/"/>
    <updated>2012-02-28T21:09:04+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/02/28/test</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>弄了差不多半个小时，把blog的嵌入代码插件弄好了：）
早上看ruby的时候了解到一些类的知识，遇到了之前python迟迟不能解决的一个问题。琢磨了一会，mission accomplished!
嗯，主要就是一个带counter的urlopener, 之前dbci的urlopener在调度上面总是实现地不怎么 &#8216;elegant&#8217;, 如今使用了带counter的urlopener，嗯。。还看得过去:)</p>

<pre><code># this is a urlopener class with a counter.
# sometimes i just this this urlopener to open urls and make schedulings based on counter

class opener_with_counter(urllib.FancyURLopener):
    #basically, it's just a URLopener class plus a counter.
    def __init__(self, *args, **kwargs):
        urllib.FancyURLopener.__init__(self, *args, **kwargs)
        self.count = 0

    # a warpper of urlopener.open.
    def open_with_counter(self, fullurl, data=None):
        self.count += 1
        return self.open(fullurl, data)
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[shit happens.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/02/27/shit-happens/"/>
    <updated>2012-02-27T06:52:39+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/02/27/shit-happens</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>i had some really really rough days lately and i think i kinda fucked up. i am not sure if i can still believe in what I&#8217;ve believed before.</p>

<p>i have really really high expectation for myself but that seems like going to become less possible , because of so many shit going on around this carpland.but, anyway, life moves on! just get some sleep and hang in there, u can make this happen even if this gets harder.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[hello world!]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/02/11/hello-world-2/"/>
    <updated>2012-02-11T03:00:57+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/02/11/hello-world-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now i am officially using this domain,</p>

<p>as u can see:</p>

<p>http://sunus.me</p>

<p>happy new year!</p>

<p>love u all!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2011, 2012; Part 2/2]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/01/22/2011-2012-part-22/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-22T00:27:06+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/01/22/2011-2012-part-22</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>humm, first of all, happy Spring Festival to all of you guys!
Since i posted Part 1/2 of 2011, 2012 some days ago and this thing kept on going on my mind: i still didn&#8217;t finished the second part of that post, so, i will do it now.:)
i got really really drunk yesterday, wasn&#8217;t i? but anyway, i am very very sober now, so i know now i am using the right words.
In 2012, i have so many goals to accomplish, i don&#8217;t know if relationship is among them.even if it&#8217;s, i will eventually put it in the last of that list.
i suddenly found out there are so many things i don&#8217;t know&#8230;.. so, gotta hurry up. and i really really don&#8217;t know what to write right now, because the whole point of writing this one is, this is the second and last part of 2011, 2012 post.and i gotta finished this because the Spring Festival so that i can embrace the future upon me:&lt;
good night and have fun!
love u all!! let&#8217;s rock 2012!!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2011, 2012; Part 1/2]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/01/02/2011-2012-part-12/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-02T01:39:42+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/01/02/2011-2012-part-12</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hi there, happy new year!</p>

<p>I just got back to my dorm several hours ago , from downtown tianjin. I was with three of my best friends celebrating the upcoming new year, 2012, and we were having great fun through the last moment of 2011</p>

<p>to the very first cup of beer of 2011. cheers!</p>

<p>so, I decided to post something to end this year and open up the new year. the title,  which I think is brilliant,  If you know  some c programming language or something called ‘comma expression’, I think you will feel the same way</p>

<p>so, here we go.</p>

<p>2011, kinda a tough year for me, even though I wrote/drawn ‘hold on’ and ‘turn on’ on my 2011 edition of QQ icon. but still. not because I made one of the biggest decision of my life on my own, but I have to deal with my problems on my own. I have to learn by myself,  I have cheer me up if I was feel upset. I have to learn to earn the every opportunity out there and finally grab some of them. sometimes I failed,</p>

<p>I told no one, then just keep on reading and learning, coding.  anyway, I learn a lot from 2011 knowledge-wise and horizon-wise.</p>

<p>the later part of 2011, I don’t think much of it. I got back to tjpu, finish my education and keep on learning. my first project ended failure, but, there’s still some people love it and feel interesting, so, not a totally  failure for me. maybe, I will re-open this project someday when time’s right. my second project is under coding now, I still have faith in that, because people need a stuff like that, to keep track of there favorite shows.</p>

<p>the good part of my returning are:</p>

<p>One:</p>

<p>I still have those two best buddies out there waiting for me and help me a lot, I even doubt that I will , some day, do the same things to the others. so, I am really really feel thankful for having you two, hoping we</p>

<p>will get really drunk one day, that the way of us to celebrating out brother-ship.</p>

<p>Two:</p>

<p>that awesome girl, again. I am just feel nothing but lucky to know her and we’re still in a very very good friendship , or it’s not just friendship, I don’t know. the point is, throughout those about three months, she’s just getting better and better. just totally a new person for me,  compare to the first day I met her.  but still, I am not that BAD, am I ?</p>

<p>I know I am a good guy, I am funny,  and I can make a girl laugh a lot while we’re hanging out, and …….</p>

<p>I am ambitious and I have very clear goal  about myself deep down in my heart, but I never talked much about it with friends. so, it’s not a surprise if a girl likes me, I know that too.</p>

<p>but, she is just awesome , I can not think about another word to describe her……</p>

<p>Three:</p>

<p>I know two geek-guy through a friend’s introduction, it’s kinda a luck , I guess. they help me a lot in exams and finally, I have someone to talk about technic stuffs in school. they just let me know, even if we’re in a crap university, there are still a few people who love what their do and will to put there times and energy into it. so, I am not alone. hope we can cooperate in the future. that’s the guy I can look for if I am ready to do something serious, and it’s the best time to find your future partner in the college. I think.</p>

<p>Sum up:</p>

<p>I met three new friends this year and I love them very much</p>

<p>even thought I failed to get the this year’s internship, which I was longing for a very long time, but just look at the bright side, I got more time to learn thing, to make new friends if I had to, so, just be patient. I think when the opportunity comes again, I am having a really good shot of grab it.</p>

<p>2011 , 2011 ; part 1/2 end.</p>

<p>To be continue.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled, just writing what i feel like to write]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2011/12/18/untitled-just-writing-what-i-feel-like-to-write/"/>
    <updated>2011-12-18T21:43:02+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2011/12/18/untitled-just-writing-what-i-feel-like-to-write</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>um&#8230; kind of feel down today and i just don&#8217;t know why.</p>

<p>lol this semester is about to finish, and i don&#8217;t know if i meet my goal that i had for this semester. no ! i know i am far away meet my goal this semester, i kind of feel frustrated about myself. didn&#8217;t do i write any popular stuffs , btw i mean the &#8216;DBCI&#8217; here, even thought there&#8217;s a few people who like it and found it interesting ,  anyway, i will NOT give up on my first project before i know how far / bigger it will get.  i decided to REFINE during my vacation.</p>

<p>i came up with a great idea several days ago, and i found my partner. so we decide to lunch this project right after we finished our exams. hopefully, my second project will do better. and i think, at least i wanna that stuff, and there is a lot of people out there who can not write codes, will need that too.</p>

<p>i had been put my most attentions on programming and internship lately, besides those stuff i really really had a very great time with a new girl i met here,  and she is the most AWESOME 18-year-old girl i know, even thought she doesn&#8217;t like to go to cinema or play billiards. i don&#8217;t know weather i will find someone else to hang out with when i just wanna see a movie or something when i have chance. i really really don&#8217;t know that either.  oh, by the way, she is gonna learn some C skills to take a exam,  i think i somehow &#8216;encourage&#8217;  her a little bit to do so.  anyway, hope she will find something interesting / beautiful in C , during the learning process.</p>

<p>i talked a lot with my friends lately,  i found that the older i get, the more i needs them and i feel very lucky to have them around, especially right now when i feel down, my best friend , still out there chatting with me, while i am writing this post.</p>

<p>i think i am kinda weird guy, i somehow will think a lot about the girl i hang out with recently, but when we lost touch one day and several days goes by. i might just forget about her and start to looking for new one.</p>

<p>i just don&#8217;t know what i am looking for. Or i just afraid to deal with the fact that i found what i am looking for,BUT i just don&#8217;t know if i deserve this ? i don&#8217;t know..</p>

<p>i wrote so many &#8216;i don&#8217;t know&#8217; in this post, i don&#8217;t know why&#8230;</p>

<p>so, good luck and happy x-mas and new year, it&#8217;s coming soon!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[first blog after i back to tjpu.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2011/11/06/136/"/>
    <updated>2011-11-06T12:19:35+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2011/11/06/136</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hey hi, long time no see again it’s been busy months after I got here. I got here early but still got soooo much crap paper work to do.when I got all of those stuffs done. I suddenly felt like , oh god. why are you get back to this crap-land and why the hell did you gain after those days?</p>

<p>when those feeling gone, I just got some ideas to keep working on my APP,aka ‘DBCI’. so the DBCI and polo fulfilled my days a lot. now the &#8216;DBCI&#8217; , I think it’s kinda like my FIRST MAJOR PROJECT , the one that I think people will actually like, feel it interesting and use it sometime for a while. as I wrote in my resume, I want to writing something that people like, I didn’t realize that day just CAME, now I just need a partner to do some UI stuff and promote it a little bit. I think it could be huge!</p>

<p>besides ‘DBCI’, I met some interesting girls that I can hang out with,that’s is just GREAT. for a guy like me don’t usually go to class , don’t usually talk to girls that not familiar with before, is hard to find girls like I have right now to hang out with. I am not saying I am not interesting or funny or attractive. I just do know where my ‘in’ is.</p>

<p>and I really really want say thank to my best brothers in tjpu, I am so so honored to know you two, I will never forget your help when I got here alone!</p>

<p>I think that’s all ! this place sucks.but I still need to find a way out, to somewhere that I truly belonged to. peace, hope my ‘DBCI’ will grow up soon and have a nice day!</p>

<p>and i just had a really nice day with you.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What kind of girl that I will ask out on a date]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2011/09/02/what-kind-of-girl-that-i-will-ask-her-out-on-a-date/"/>
    <updated>2011-09-02T21:56:04+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2011/09/02/what-kind-of-girl-that-i-will-ask-her-out-on-a-date</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A little tip:</p>

<p>If you are a guy , or you are NOT into me at all, you can just ignore this blog.</p>

<p>yeah, i figure i have to finished this post before i get going..</p>

<p>i said &#8220;i must get a serious girlfriends this semester!&#8221; some time ago to a friend , and i have some requirements for this very special girl.</p>

<p>First of all:</p>

<p>you MUST be gook-looking, i mean you can be cute, be beautiful,be attractive or sexy . that&#8217;s all right . if i ask you out  to a movie or dinner, that means I think she is GOOD-LOOKING to ME!</p>

<p>then, here comes the second stage, i want you to have some of these qualities list below :</p>

<p>(these are the ones that really matter to me, more important than your appearance)</p>

<p>0: don&#8217;t be evil.</p>

<p>1: thoughtful and considerate to others</p>

<p>2: have ability to think independently, have your own opinions</p>

<p>3: have good sense of humor</p>

<p>4: at least have basic computer skill, if you are a coder, programmer-to-be or computer science relevant major , that&#8217;s just great . if you like      writing programs/codes , or research in ALGORITHM, that&#8217;s just AWESOME!!!!!(i really mean it, that&#8217;s what a girl that i longing for days looks like) and i won&#8217;t repair your computer/phones for more than 3 TIMES!</p>

<p>5: love movies or American TV shows like:</p>

<p>[24, The big bang theory,  How i met your mother, Leverage,  It crowds,  Spartacus, Gossip girl and PORNS:D:D!!]</p>

<p>then we may have more topic to chat about.</p>

<p>6: knowing stuffs, like how two people to maintain their relationship, what can do and what can NOT do, that&#8217;s important especially when we</p>

<p>decided to start a relationship.</p>

<p>7: respect people&#8217;s privacy, that mean i will NEVER give out my IM account, Email account, Social Networks account, etc. and i won&#8217;t ask you</p>

<p>for these infos, neither.</p>

<p>8: if you are a Hardcore Counter-Strike player , polo beginner or a programmer/coder , that will SIGNIFICANTLY  increase my impression of you.</p>

<p>9:at lease understand what i wrote above , with or without the help of any kinds of TRANSLATOR. i know there&#8217;s a lot a grammar mistake inside this blog,  if you can point it out, i appreciate it</p>

<p>Lastly, please do keep this in mind:</p>

<p>if i ask you out to a movie or dinner for the FIRST time, it just , just means i think you are good-looking to me, nothing less, nothing more.It takes days to build up a serious relationship.</p>

<p>thanks  for reading this long piece-of-crap-blog-if-you-are-not-into-me lol</p>

<p>have a good day! sweetie!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
