<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: life | What happens here, stays in here.]]></title>
  <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://sunus.me/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-09T21:58:26+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://sunus.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[sunus]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[0x16]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/25/0x16/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-25T08:31:32+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/25/0x16</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>humm, i feel like i am not young anymore. but, i am still doing those 'young people' stuffs that i really really feel some kinda ashamed of. so, it's time to grow up. in fact, i know i am growing up with time goes by.
in this very moment, right before i turn to 0x16, i would like to post something, something that i wanted to say several days ago.
first of all, i am so grateful for my family for they gave me a very very nice childhood. even though sometimes i felt it just not enough, but deep down in my heart, i knew they did what they could and i will always grateful for what they've gave to me. i just love to have them around me!
second, i'd like to thank all of my friends, for the time we spent together, for the happiness and sadness we shared. i'm really really proud of having you guys. I will do everything i can to make you feel the same way as i do, that is, i am hoping one day, you will feel proud of having me as your friend.
one last thing, i also want to end this with something suddenly came up of my head several days ago,  to my family,  friends and the ones i love:</p>

<p>i am trying hard to to a guy that deserves you.</p>

<p>because you are just so AMAZING.</p>

<p>hope i will not let you guys down before i turn to 0x17.</p>

<p>good night:)</p>

<p>END OF 0x15.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[i'd rather take 951 than 871.]]></title>
    <link href="http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/11/id-rather-take-951-than-871/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-11T08:27:40+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://sunus.me/blog/2012/03/11/id-rather-take-951-than-871</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hi, i've got a busy week, and i still got a lot of codes to write and i am happy that i still got something to do.
the project tmenny is about to launch and my resume-generator is almost finished. in the very beginning,  i was about to write it in ruby,which i just learned those days. but quickly i found out i might do this in the language i love most, that is, C. so,i wrote so much more lines of codes than ruby/python but i love the way C codes works. simple, clear and fast. and i can figure out almost what is going on under the every line of codes.that is just feels good!</p>

<p>humm, i really miss the days when we ACTUALLY hang out together last semester. sometime i don't feel the same way
as we're in school while i teach you some programming stuffs or just walk with you,strange.
even though i met someone new and we had great time, still i would rather going out taking 951 with you.</p>

<p>SK failed again and some of my really good friends are going to leave this school, including the one i just met, which is pretty sad for my to accept.</p>

<p>i am not quite quitting counter-strike yet, as we haven't been 'actually' 'hang out' lately, it's fun playing counter-strike on lan. but if i got chance hanging out with you, i will definitely pick you for sure. it's just 10 times fun than just playing game with nine guys :&lt;</p>

<p>hoping i can getting in 951 soon.
good night, gotta code tomorrow.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
